This is a day in a life of tired
disabled student in South Korea.
>> Hi, I'm Jiyu. I drank a lot yesterday,
so I woke up a bit late. Since I work as
a content creator, I received a PR
package for menstrual product to try
out. Thank you, [screaming] Happy
Monday. [cheering] Then I took a shower
and did my skin care routine.
I picked this blush because I'm wearing
a red top today. I have to return all
these books, so I carried them down and
threw them in the trash bin. Just
kidding, it's a book return box. Then I
headed to the cafe to meet a friend
[music] who was my TA back in America.
After that, I took a bus back home. It
was pretty unusual for me, but
surprisingly, it was super accessible
and the driver was so nice. I was
planning to film in the library, but it
was closed, so I just stayed at home
instead. Lastly, I wrapped up my day
doing an interview, and that was my day.